A Guide to the Marcia A. T. Thompson papers FA1489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts Stabilization Projects, 1936-2000; 3; 12.99 Cubic Feet 28 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes
  - GATX Corporation - 1981-1985 Operating Budget; 1981 Capital Budget - The National Arts Stabilization Fund, Inc. - Compensation Committee Meeting, 1986 December 11 (Box 34, Folder 357)
    Personnel Material
  - Manhattan Theatre Club Long Range Plan - Salary Review, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 358)
    Personnel Information
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Compensation Committee - April 2, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Stabilization Analyses, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Arizona Project Comments Binder - Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Baltimore Project Comments Binder - Correspondence and Remarks by Walter Sondheim, Member of the Board, The Abell Foundation, Baltimore Arts Stabilization Announcement, 1993 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Seattle Project Comments Binder - Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Communications Materials, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Ford Foundation - National Poetry Series, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Interactive Management System Forms, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Newspaper/Article Clippings and Comics, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Assessment of Nominees, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Boston Stabilization Project Tickler, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Personnel Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Catch: Baseball Season at The New York Public Library mailer, undated (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Non-Sexist Language Guidelines by Alma Graham, 1974 August (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Excuses for a Closed Mind, New York Chapter of the American Society of Training Directors, undated (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Ford Foundation Stabilization Programs I and II At-a-Glance Index, 1984-1993 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Consumer Price Indexes, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - More Poems by Peter W. Culman, 1975 December (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Doodles, 1967-1976 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Consulting Rates, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund Staff, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 359)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund Staffing, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 360)
  - Statistics - from Articles and Reports, 1981-1993 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Statistics: Consumer Price Index, 1977-1986 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Statistics - Arts Organizations, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Project Fees, 1986-1992 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - G&A/First Phase, The - Reactions, 1976-1993 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Board of Directors (2 folders), 1983-1992 (Box 11, Folder 120-121)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Database - Spreadsheets - Annual Review Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    Analysis of organizations - ballets, museums, opera, orchestras, professional training, theatres, 1989-1990
    Analysis of grants and gifts by source - ranked by grants and gifts as a percentage of expenses
    Analysis of Boston granteesm 1981-1990
    NASF Database Study and Analysis
  - Jobs and Analyses, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Joffrey Ballet and Houston Ballet pamphlets, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Brockway, George, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Letters to Marcia Aldrich Thompson Thompson, 1961-1993 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Agreements, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Corporate Council Celebrates the Arts, 1986-1992 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Administrative Documents, 1986-1993 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Forms, Guidelines, and Analysis, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Staff List, 1991 October (Box 35, Folder 361)
  - Common Investment Fund for Foundations - Council on Foundations, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Gerety, Edward, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Clippings, 1983-1992 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Review of Grantees and Proposed Changes to Forms, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Ballet and Dance Balance Sheets, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    The Foundation for the Joffrey Ballet, Inc.
    State Ballet of Missouri
    Dance Theatre of Harlem
    Pacific Northwest Ballet
  - The Chronicle of Philanthropy, 1992 September 8 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Loose Financial Planning Templates, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - The Burden of the Ford Foundation, Kristin A. Goss, The Chronicle of Philanthropy, 1992 May 4 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - St. Paul Opera Association Evaluation, 1977 March 3 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - ASOL Data Bank - Major Symphony Orchestra Program 1971-1972 through 1975-1976, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - The National Arts Stabilization Fund - Meeting of the Board of Directors - Agenda and Items, 1992 September 15 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Database and Boxscore Report (2 folders), 1991 March (Box 13, Folder 143-144)
    Originially in binders - sections include:
    Current Boxscore
    Database Runs - Alphabetical - 1. Ranked by Aggregate Profile $; 2. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
    Budget/Expenses - 3. Ranked by Aggregate Profile $; 4. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
    Geographical - 5. Ranked by Aggregate Profile $; 6. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
    Discipline and Expenses - 7. Ranked by Aggregate Profile; 8. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
    Discipline and Rank - 9. Ranked by Aggregate Profile $; 10. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
    Rank - 11. Ranked by Aggregate Profile $; 12. Ranked by Aggregate Profile as Percent of Expenses
  - Accordion Work Organizer - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, 1977-1998 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Project Data, 1993 November (Box 13, Folder 146)
    1. Nominees - By Project Site
    2. Nominees - By Discipline
    3. Nominees - By Year
    4. Nominees - Current Active Nominees
    5. Grantees - Awards to Date (November 1993)
    6. Grantees - By Project Site
    7. Grantees - By Discipline
    8. Grantees - By Year
    9. Grantees - Elapsed Time Between Nomination and Award
    10. Grantees - Grant Terms Ended/Ending Dates
    11. Grantees - At-a-Glance Sample Snapshot
    12. Project Sites - Boston Chronology, Committee, and Donors
    13. Project Sites - Kansas City Chronology, Committee and Donors
    14. Project Sites - Arizona Chronology, Committee and Donors
    15. Project Sites - Seattle Chronology, Committee and Donors
    16. Project Sites - NYC Chronology, Committee and Donors
    17. Project Sites - Baltimore Chronology, Committee and Donors
    18. Project Sites - Project Development Summary
    19. Project Sites - Project Development: A Panoramic View
    20. Donors - Numerical Summary
    21. Potential Project Sites - Investigated by NASF
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Working Off Balance: A Dialogue on Arts Stabilization, Columbus, Ohio - Conference Information and Reading Materials, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Feld Ballets NY/Original Ballets Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Tactical Operating Plans, Strategic Plans, and 10th Anniversary Report Task Force, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Five-Year Strategic Plan, 1993-1997, 1993 March-April (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Computer Systems Planning Schedules - National Arts Stabilization Fund Masters - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    Three copies of the NASF Five Year Strategic Plan, 1993-1997, Phase One
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning (4 folders), 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 152, Box 15, Folder 153-155)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Ford Foundation Consultants (2 folders), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 156-157)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning Handouts, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    Handout #1 - Minutes of Long-Range Planning Meeting, December 17, 1992
    Handout #2 - Long-Range Planning Process Chronology and Timeframe
    Handout #3 - NASF Publications and Background Documents
    Handout #4 - By-Laws of NASF - Original and Amendment
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning - Drafts, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 159)
    Advisory Group Letters
    Draft Outlines
    Long-Range Plan Drafts
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning - Board Meeting Materials, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Financial Documents, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 161)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Finance Committee, 1992 December 2 (Box 16, Folder 162)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Vision Statement, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 163)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning (2 folders), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 164-165)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning (2 folders), 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 166-167)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Meetings (5 folders), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 169, Box 17, Folder 170-173)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Long-Range Planning Committee (3 folders), 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 174-176)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Topics of Interest and Concern, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - The Arts: Politics, Power and the Purse - An International Conference on the Structure of Arts Funding, The Arts Council, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    Marcia Thompson mentioned pages 28-30
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Draft - Syracuse, NY, 1984 May (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Congratulatory Letters, 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Common Fund 2nd, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 181)
  - Remarks of Marcia Thompson at the International Conference on the Structure of Arts Funding, London, 1987 March 4 (Box 18, Folder 182)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Remarks and Notes for Visits to Kansas City, Seattle and Phoenix, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 183)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Administrative Documents, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 184)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Notes, Awards Approved as of July 1, 1991, and Nominees by Discipline as of September 1, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - American Council for the Arts, 1986 August 7 (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - Arts Council of Great Britain, London (2 folders), 1987 March 4-5 (Box 18, Folder 187-188)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Arizona Announcement, 1989 January-February (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - New York City, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Boston, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Lyric Opera of Chicago - Women's Board, 1983 January 25 (Box 18, Folder 192)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Seattle, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - Ford Foundation Meeting and Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    Ford Board of Trustees Meeting - June 23, 1983
    Education and Culture Committee - Marcia Thompson Opening Remarks, March 24, 1982
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Kansas City Remarks - W. M. Ellinghaus and Marcia Thompson, 1986 April 13 (Box 18, Folder 195)
  - Seattle City Club, 1989 February 16 (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Remarks, Drafts of Reports, and Long-Range Planning Materials (2 folders), 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 197, Box 19, Folder 198)
  - Dallas, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Marcia Thompson Notes for Speakers (2 folders), 1978-1990 (Box 19, Folder 200-201)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Reports, Notes, Correspondence, and Ford Foundation Discussion, 1972-1993 (Box 19, Folder 202)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Report Drafts, Notes, and Remarks (2 folders), 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 203-204)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Remarks and Reports with Edits and Notes (4 folders), 1982-1986 (Box 19, Folder 205-206, Box 20, Folder 207-208)
  - Ford Foundation Stabilization Program and National Arts Stabilization Fund - Background, Remarks, and Report Drafts (4 folders), 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 209-212)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Drafts of Speeches and Reports, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - The Acting Company (3 folders), 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 214, Box 21, Folder 215-216)
  - Arts Economic Impact, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 217)
  - Arts Giving Statistics, 1994 January (Box 21, Folder 218)
    1. The Conference Board
    2. Giving USA
    3. Corporations
    4. Foundations
    5. NEA/NEH Appropriations
    6. State Arts Councils (NASAA)
    7. Local Arts Councils (NALAA)
    8. United Arts Funds
    9. Charitable Giving: Cities and Regional Trends
  - Arts Operating Statistics, 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 219)
    1. National Statistics and Trends
    2. CPI Data
    3. Cities/Project Sites
    4. Art Museums
    5. Dance
    6. Opera
    7. Professional Training
    8. Symphony Orchestra
    9. Theater
  - Audit Reports (2 folders), 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 220-221)
    City Center 55th Street Theater Foundation
    Black Spectrum Theatre Company
    Circle Repertory Theater Company
    The Vivian Beaumont Theater
    Marlboro School of Music
    Music-Theatre Group, Inc. and Lenox Arts Center, Inc.
    New York City Opera, Inc.
    The National Theatre of the Deaf
    The Pierpont Morgan Library
    New York City Ballet
    Theatre Communications Group
  - Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB), 1993 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - Long Range Plans (LRPs) (2 folders), 1983-1993 (Box 21, Folder 223-224)
    Houston Ballet
    Seattle Opera Association
    Huntington Theatre Company
    Baltimore Opera
    Seattle Symphony
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Applause, 1983-1992 (Box 22, Folder 225-226)
    Copies of correspondence
  - National Dance Institute (NDI), 1994 (Box 22, Folder 227)
  - National Dance Institute - Rosebud's Song, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 228)
  - National Dance Institute - Financial Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 229)
  - National Theatre of the Deaf, 1988-1993 (Box 22, Folder 230)
  - Nonprofit Facilities Fund, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - Philanthropy Clippings, 1981-1993 (Box 22, Folder 232)
  - Increasing Private Sector Cultural Support: Opportunities for Federal Policies and Action, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 233)
  - Scherman Foundation (2 folders), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 234-235)
  - Scherman Foundation - Meeting Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 236)
  - Shakin Lichty and Boreyko, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 237)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program - Annual Report Comments, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program/Orchestra Audit Collection at Ford Foundation Archives - G&A Status Reports, 1984 November-1985 August (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - Symphony Orchestras - Autopsy of an Orchestra: An Analysis of Factors Contributing to the Bankruptcy of the Oakland Symphony Association, Melanie Beene and Associates, M. Melanie Beene, Fenton Johnson, Patricia A. Mitchell, 1988 January (Box 23, Folder 240)
  - Symphony Orchestras - Analysis, 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 241)
  - Symphony Orchestras - Clippings and Reports (3 folders), 1988-1993 (Box 23, Folder 242-244)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation Symphony Orchestra Program - Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 245)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 1983-1994 (Box 23, Folder 246)
  - Worksheets (2 folders), 1984-1993 (Box 23, Folder 247-248)
    American Ballet Theatre
    Ballet Hispanico
    Cunningham Dance Foundation
    Paul Taylor Dance
    Baltimore Symphony
    Boston Ballet
    Boston Ballet School
    Cincinnati Ballet
    Center Stage
    Arizona Theatre Company
    Juillard
    National Theatre For The Deaf
    Pacific NW Ballet
    Pennsylvania Ballet
    Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre
    San Francisco Ballet
    New York City Opera
  - Audit Reports and Financial Statements (2 folders), 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 249-250)
    The Joyce Theater Foundation, Inc.
    Dance Theater Foundation
    Scenic Hudson
    Spanish Theatre Repertory Company
    Bronx Museum of the Arts
  - Audit Reports, Financial Statements, and Correspondence (2 folders), 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 251-252)
    The Museum for Africa Art
    Classic Stage Company Repertory
    The Frick Collection
    Original Ballets Foundation
  - New York City Ballet - Financial Statements (3 folders), 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 253-255)
  - New York City Ballet - Financial Review Drafts, Worksheets, and Analyses, 1989-1992 (Box 25, Folder 256)
  - New York City Ballet - Spring Season 1994, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 257)
  - New York City Ballet and City Center of Music and Drama - Financial and Fundraising Information, 1974-1991 (Box 25, Folder 258)
  - New York City Ballet - Donations and Grants, 1983-1992 (Box 25, Folder 259)
  - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc.: An Exposition, Analysis and Four Year Projection Prepared as an Application to the Ford Foundation on Behalf of the New York City Ballet and the New York City Opera, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 260)
  - Ford Foundation Grant to The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Correspondence, Program Action Documents, and Application, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 261)
  - Ford Foundation Grant to The City Center of Drama and Music, Inc. - Correspondence and Grant Materials, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 262)
  - City Center of Music and Drama - Program Action Forms and Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 263)
  - Ford Foundation Ballet Development, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 264)
  - New York City Ballet, 1962-1986 (Box 25, Folder 265)
  - New York City Ballet - Meetings and Memos (2 folders), 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 266-267)
  - New York City Ballet - Press Releases, Notes, and Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 268)
  - The George Balanchine Trust, 1987-1993 (Box 25, Folder 269)
  - New York City Ballet Board of Directors, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - New York City Ballet Correspondence, 1976-1993 (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - New York City Ballet Long Range Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - New York City Ballet Long Range Planning Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - New York City Ballet Board Invitations, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - New York City Ballet News Coverage, 1979-1994 (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - New York City Ballet Program Notes, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - New York City Ballet Subscription (2 folders), 1984-1992 (Box 26, Folder 277-278)
  - New York City Ballet - Long Range Planning (6 folders), 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 279, Box 27, Folder 280-284)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, Saratoga Springs, New York, 1992 July 18 (Box 27, Folder 285)
    Sections include:
    Bob Lipp's Marketing Presentation (overheads)
    Agenda
    Artistic Program
    Marketing
    Outreach: Press/Public Relations
    Development
    Outreach: Touring
    Outreach: Video/Media
    Outreach: Education
  - New York City Ballet, Cincinnati Ballet, and Maryland Institute College of Art - Financial Analysis, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - New York City Ballet - Strategic Planning Committee (2 folders), 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 287-288)
  - The School of the American Ballet (2 copies of the report), 1982 January 25 (Box 28, Folder 289)
  - New York City Ballet - Long-Range Planning/Task Group Reports and Development Attachments, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 290)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Board of Directors, Planning Documents, Financial Statements, 1986-1994 (Box 28, Folder 291)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Board Meeting Materials and Ballet Arizona, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 292)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Miscellaneous Board of Directors Documents, Correspondence, and Staff Memos, 1982-1994 (Box 28, Folder 293)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Miscellaneous Documents - Board Meetings and Correspondence, Discussion Papers, and Reports (4 folders), 1970-1994 (Box 28, Folder 294-297)
  - Consultants and Part-Time Staff, 1989-1992 (Box 29, Folder 298)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Goals, Etc., 1993-1997 (Box 29, Folder 299)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Staff/Personnel Committees (3 folders), 1985-1993 (Box 29, Folder 300-302)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Staff (2 folders), 1985-1991 (Box 29, Folder 303-304)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Project Finances, 1987-1993 (Box 29, Folder 305)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - New York City Project, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 306)
  - Resumes, 1977-1991 (Box 35, Folder 362)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1992 June 16 (Box 30, Folder 307)
  - School of American Ballet and New York City Ballet - Pamphlets, Handbooks, and Programs, 1989-2005 (Box 30, Folder 308)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 309)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 310)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 311)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 312)
  - Copies of Correspondence from Lincoln Center/City Center/Juilliard, 1960-1985 (Box 30, Folder 313)
  - National Program - Problems and Praise, 1964-1974 (Box 30, Folder 314)
  - School of American Ballet - FY 2004 Minutes (2 folders), 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 315-316)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 317)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 318)
  - School of American Ballet - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 319)
  - School of American Ballet - Correspondence and Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 320)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 321)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 322)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 323)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 324)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 325)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 326)
  - School of American Ballet - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - New York City Ballet - Annual Reports, Newsletters, and Press Releases, 1999-2005 (Box 31, Folder 328)
  - New York City Ballet - Press Releases, Correspondence, Clippings, and Pamphlets (2 folders), 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 329-330)
    Includes materials related to the New York City Ballet's 50th anniversary celebrations
  - School of American Ballet - Financial Reports and Correspondence (4 folders), 1965-1974 (Box 32, Folder 331-334)
  - Copies of Ford Foundation Grant Files Related to Ballet Initiatives (5 folders), 1959-1975 (Box 32, Folder 335-339)
  - Ballet Society Survey, undated (Box 33, Folder 340)